If your submitted data package needs further revision
you will find it under the status "Needs Rework".
To figure out why your package was rejected, use the "Settings" symbol.
Here you can find the reviews of your data curator.
If you want to edit your package, for example to add some additional data,
use the Edit project button in the top right-hand corner.
Your data package is now back in the edit mode.
Here you can add further data, and delete or restructure your data as required.
You can find more information on how to edit your data under "Editor".
To leave the edit mode, use the back arrow.
If necessary, you can also edit the metadata here by using the book symbol.
Once you have completed the revision of your data package,
you can submit it again for review using the "Submit package" button.
The package is now again shown under "In Review".
If a further revision is necessary and the responsible curator rejects your package again,
you will find it under the status "Needs Rework".
If your data package requires no further revision,
the curator will submit it directly to the archive.
Your data package will then appear with the status "Archived".
Please note that at this point you will no longer be able to edit your data.